degreescholar.com 2013-06-05

# Degree Scholar

DegreeScholar.com understands that you are concerned about how your information is used and shared. This notice explains our privacy policy and how your information may or may not be used by our site.

By visiting DegreeScholar.com you are accepting the terms described in our privacy policy. 

**What personal information about customers does DegreeScholar.com gather?**  
Information we gather on our site helps us enhance the experience that future visitors may have on our site. Here are the types of information we gather: 

**Does DegreeScholar.com share the information we receive?**  
Information about our customers is very important to us. We do reserve the right to sell the information to other parties if you willfully agree to be part of our newsletter. However, we will only disclose your email address. 

The information that is submitted to each school is not subject to being sold to anyone else except the school you have requested information from. Our relationships and contracts with the schools prohibit us from contacting you directly without your expressed consent. 

**What sort of Information might I receive from DegreeScholar.com?**  
If you do opt-in to our newsletter, we may on occasion send out information that we deem of interest to you. This could range from helpful hints about education to other advertising offers such as but not limited to loan offers, and/or consumer product offers. 

**What information can I access?**  
DegreeScholar.com fully believes in transparency and accessibility. If you wish to delete your information from our database, please send a written request to [contactus@DegreeScholar.com](mailto:contactus@theeducationedge.com) and your request will be processed within 3 business days. 

If you wish to remove your contact information from a particular school, you must contact that school directly. You can also email us, and we will forward on your request to the appropriate representatives at each school. It usually takes about 1 week for all parties to comply with your request. 

**Are Children allowed to use DegreeScholar.com?**  
All people are allowed to access and use our site. However, since we market education for adult learners, we usually require the person to be at least 18 years old to submit an request for information.

**How safe is my information?**  
At DegreeScholar.com we currently do not collect information such as social security numbers or credit card numbers. If we do in the future change this policy, we will ensure that this information is transmitted in a secure environment. At the moment, we only collect information that is publicly accessible and can often be found in phone books or internet search engines. Therefore, we currently do not offer SSL encryption on our site. 

**If I have a problem with my data, how can I resolve it?**  
We are committed to helping you resolve your dilemma as quickly as possible. Please contact us through email at [contactus@DegreeScholar.com](mailto:contactus@theeducationedge.com). This email box is checked during business working days only. We are committed to resolving any issues in a timely manner. 

**Conditions of Use**  
By using and accessing DegreeScholar.com you are agreeing to the Online Privacy Policy set forth. As our business changes and grows, we may change the privacy policy. Any changes will be posted on our site. Please check back often for any updates.

Sincerely,

The DegreeScholar.com Team
